yamarkets.com 2019-12-15

# 

                                        Privacy Policy
Protecting the privacy and safeguarding the personal and financial information of our clients and
website visitors is one of our highest priorities. The following Privacy Statement explains how
YAMARKETS LIMITED collects and protects your personal information.
By opening a YAMARKETS LIMITED account or by using YAMARKETS LIMITED websites, you give your
consent to the collection and use of personal information by YAMARKETS LIMITED as explained in this
Privacy Statement.
Collection of personal information
We collect your personal information directly from you and indirectly as a result of your relationship
with us. YAMARKETS LIMITED may use the information collected from you to verify your identity and
contact information, establish your trading account, issue you an account number and a secure
password, maintain your account activity and contact you with account information, among other
reasons. This information also helps us improve our services to you, customize your browsing
experience and inform you about additional products, services or promotions that may be of interest to
you.
You directly provide us with the majority of information we collect. This information includes your
contact details, including name, mailing address, telephone number and e-mail address, personal
identification data we are required by law to collect, including your passport number and/or tax
identification number, and information required by law to assess your trading experience and risk
tolerance, including your annual income, net worth and available risk capital. We also collect
demographic information when you open an account, including gender, birth date, occupation and
employment status.
You provide us with this information by completing the account application and related documentation,
by sending us an e-mail or by submitting information in response to a promotion or special offer.
The information we collect indirectly from you includes your Internet protocol ("IP") address, browser
type, operating system, Internet service provider (ISP), time stamps and transaction history.
Should you close your account with us, YAMARKETS LIMITED will retain your information, but only use it
to comply with regulatory requirements and to periodically contact you to offer you the opportunity to
reactivate your account or participate in other offers.
Cookies
We use cookies and web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies
(collectively, "cookies") to provide us with data we can use to improve your experience and to know you
better. Cookies are small text files sent from Web servers that may be stored on your computer. Cookies
enable us to capture how you arrived at our site, when you return, which pages on our site you visit, and

to recognize that you are already logged on when we receive a page request from your browser. We
may link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on
our site. We will never share this information with any 3rd party. Cookies are readable only by us and do
not contain any personal information nor do they contain account or password information. We cannot
and will not gather information about other sites you may have visited.
We may share usage information about visitors to our websites with reputable advertising companies
for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements. The information collected by the
advertising company through the use of these pixel tags is not personally identifiable. We may also use
3rd party software to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information including page
requests, form requests and click paths. The third party may use cookies to track behavior and may set
cookies on behalf of YAMARKETS LIMITED.
All web browsers have settings that allow you to block cookies. By visiting our website with your
browser set to allow cookies, you consent to our use of cookies as described above. If you choose to
block cookies you may use our services but some functions may not work as designed.
Sharing Personal Information with YAMARKETS LIMITED
affiliates and Non-affiliated third parties
YAMARKETS LIMITED does not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose your personal information to any
affiliate or third party for any reason, except as described below.
YAMARKETS LIMITED may share information with affiliates if the information is required to provide the
product or service you have requested or to provide you the opportunity to participate in the products
or services our affiliates offer.
To help us improve our services to you, we may engage another business to help us carry out certain
internal functions, such as account processing, fulfillment, client service, client satisfaction surveys or
other data collection activities relevant to our business. We may also provide a non-affiliated third party
with client information from our database, including your name, address, phone number, and/or e-mail
address, to help us analyze and identify client needs, notify clients of product and service offerings or
conduct general marketing and market research for us.
YAMARKETS LIMITED also forges partnerships and alliances with non-affiliated third parties which offer
high-quality products and services that might be of value to our clients. In order to ensure that these
products and services meet your needs and are delivered in a manner that is useful and relevant,
YAMARKETS LIMITED may share some personal information with these non-affiliated third parties.
We generally require that all non-affiliated third parties to which we provide your nonpublic personal
information agree to keep your information confidential and use such information solely for the limited

purpose for which we have engaged them, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, where offers are
made to you by non-affiliated third parties, we generally require that they disclose that the offer is being
extended because of your relationship with us. We also seek to ensure that these non-affiliated third
parties maintain appropriate data security procedures to guard against unauthorized use of, or access
to, your personal information.
When required by law, YAMARKETS LIMITED reserves the right to disclose your personal information to
third parties or regulatory, law enforcement or other government authorities. We may also disclose
your information to credit reporting or collection agencies, or when necessary to protect our rights or
property.
If at any time you choose to purchase a product or service offered by another company, for example by
clicking on an advertisement on a website owned or controlled by YAMARKETS LIMITED, any personal
information you share with that company will no longer be controlled under our Privacy Statement. We
are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of sites we link to and we have no control over
the use or protection of information provided by you to, or collected by, those websites. Whenever you
elect to link to a co-branded website or to a linked website, you may be asked to provide registration or
other information. Please note that the information you are providing is going to a third party, and you
should familiarize yourself with the privacy policy published by that third party.
The security of your personal information
We employ security software, systems and procedures to offer you a safe and secure trading
environment and to protect your personal, financial and trading information.
When you open an account with us, you are issued a unique account number, User ID and a password.
Only a limited number of YAMARKETS LIMITED employees who have a need to know this information
will have access to your account number, UserID, and password. Remember that you are ultimately
responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your account number, UserID and password. We strongly
recommend that you do not disclose this information to anyone.
On our websites and online account application we use technology to encrypt information transmitted
by or to you. We use certificate authority (CA) certificates to authenticate our websites and secure
trading and customer-facing applications, allowing you to verify that you are connected to our websites.
Changes to this Privacy Statement and Opting Out
In the event YAMARKETS LIMITED materially changes this Privacy Statement, the revised Privacy
Statement will promptly be posted to our websites. By opening an account with us, you are deemed to
agree to accept posting of a revised Privacy Statement electronically on our website as actual notice to
you.

Under certain circumstances, such as with respect to our sharing of your personal information with non-
affiliated third parties, you may inform us that you would like to "opt out" by contacting us through the
contact information listed below. Note that for joint accounts, an-opt out election made by one account
owner of a joint account is applicable to all account owners of the joint account. An opt-out election
must be made for each separate account you hold at YAMARKETS LIMITED.
Any dispute over our Privacy Statement is subject to this notice and the YAMARKETS LIMITED Customer
Agreement. If you have any questions that this Privacy Statement does not address, please contact a
Client Services representative.
You may contact YAMARKETS LIMITED for any reason under this Privacy Statement, or otherwise, as
follows:
